export default [
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20colossal%20titan%20in%20%22Attack%20On%20Titan%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Bertolt%20Hoover",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Reiner", "Eren", "Sasha"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20Funny%20Valentine%27s%20stand%20in%20Jojo%27s%20Bizarre%20Adventure%20Part%207%2C%20Steel%20Ball%20Run%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Dirty%20Deeds%20Done%20Dirt%20Cheap",
    "incorrect_answers":
      [
        "Filthy%20Acts%20Done%20For%20A%20Reasonable%20Price",
        "Civil%20War",
        "God%20Bless%20The%20USA",
      ],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20main%20heroine%20of%20the%20anime%2C%20Full%20Metal%20Panic%21",
    "correct_answer": "Kaname%20Chidori",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Teletha%20Testarossa", "Melissa%20Mao", "Kyoko%20Tokiwa"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "The%20two%20main%20characters%20of%20%22No%20Game%20No%20Life%22%2C%20Sora%20and%20Shiro%2C%20together%20go%20by%20what%20name%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Blank",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Immanity", "Disboard", "Warbeasts"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20last%20name%20of%20Edward%20and%20Alphonse%20in%20the%20Fullmetal%20Alchemist%20series.",
    "correct_answer": "Elric",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Ellis", "Eliek", "Elwood"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "The%20name%20of%20Junko%20Enoshima%27s%20imposter%20at%20the%20beginning%20of%20Danganronpa%3A%20Trigger%20Happy%20Havoc%20is%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Mukuro%20Ikusaba",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Ryota%20Mitarai", "Ultimate%20Imposter", "Komaru%20Naegi"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Which%20of%20the%20folwing%20originated%20as%20a%20manga%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Akira",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Cowboy%20Bebop", "High%20School%20DxD", "Gurren%20Lagann"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "On%20what%20medium%20was%20%22Clannad%22%20first%20created%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Visual%20novel",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Anime", "Manga", "Light%20novel"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "In%20the%20anime%20Seven%20Deadly%20Sins%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20one%20of%20the%20sins%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Diane",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Sakura", "Ayano", "Sheska"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20year%20did%20%22Attack%20on%20Titan%22%20first%20air%3F",
    "correct_answer": "2013",
    "incorrect_answers": ["2014", "2012", "2015"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Who%20was%20given%20the%20title%20%22Full%20Metal%22%20in%20the%20anime%20series%20%22Full%20Metal%20Alchemist%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Edward%20Elric",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Alphonse%20Elric", "Van%20Hohenheim", "Izumi%20Curtis"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "In%20Digimon%2C%20what%20is%20the%20Japanese%20name%20for%20the%20final%20evolutionary%20stage%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Ultimate",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Mega", "Adult", "Champion"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20corgi%20in%20Cowboy%20Bebop%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Einstein",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Edward", "Rocket", "Joel"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "In%20%22To%20Love-Ru%22%2C%20Ren%20and%20Run%20are%20from%20what%20planet%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Memorze",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Deviluke", "Mistletoe", "Okiwana"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20armored%20titan%20in%20%22Attack%20On%20Titan%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Reiner%20Braun",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Armin%20Arlelt", "Mikasa%20Ackermann", "Eren%20Jaeger"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "In%20%22Fairy%20Tail%22%2C%20what%20is%20the%20nickname%20of%20Natsu%20Dragneel%3F",
    "correct_answer": "The%20Salamander",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["The%20Dragon%20Slayer", "The%20Dragon", "The%20Demon"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "How%20many%20%22JoJos%22%20that%20are%20protagonists%20are%20there%20in%20the%20series%20%22Jojo%27s%20Bizarre%20Adventure%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "8%2B",
    "incorrect_answers": ["6%2B", "4%2B", "5%2B"],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20name%20is%20the%20main%20character%20Chihiro%20given%20in%20the%202001%20movie%20%22Spirited%20Away%22%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Sen%20%28Thousand%29",
    "incorrect_answers":
      [
        "Hyaku%20%28Hundred%29",
        "Ichiman%20%28Ten%20thousand%29",
        "Juu%20%28Ten%29",
      ],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "What%20caused%20the%20titular%20mascot%20of%20Yo-Kai%20Watch%2C%20Jibanyan%2C%20to%20become%20a%20yokai%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Being%20run%20over%20by%20a%20truck",
    "incorrect_answers":
      [
        "Ate%20one%20too%20many%20chocobars",
        "Through%20a%20magical%20ritual",
        "When%20he%20put%20on%20the%20harmaki",
      ],
  },
  {
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "category": "Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
    "question": "Who%20is%20the%20true%20moon%20princess%20in%20Sailor%20Moon%3F",
    "correct_answer": "Sailor%20Moon",
    "incorrect_answers":
      ["Sailor%20Venus", "Sailor%20Mars", "Sailor%20Jupiter"],
  },
];
